Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Zines, 1964-2009, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, June, 1995; cuid23892 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Aug., 1995; cuid23893 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Sept., 1995; cuid23894 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1995; cuid23895 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1995; cuid23896 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb., 1996; cuid23897 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, March, 1996; cuid23898 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, July, 1996; cuid23899 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Sept., 1996; cuid23900 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Oct., 1996; cuid23901 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1996; cuid23902 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1996; cuid23903 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb., 1997; cuid23904 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, March, 1997; cuid23905 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, May, 1997; cuid23906 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Aug., 1997; cuid23907 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2001. v.4, cuid23908 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2001. v.8, cuid23909 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2002. v.9, cuid23910 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2007. v.15, cuid23911 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs by Julius: Back Alley Graffiti. California, Avenue Services, 1994; cuid23912 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Handjobs by Julius: Bavarian Chronicles I, the Legacy of Slava. California, Avenue Services, 1995; cuid23913 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Handjobs Presents Bedtime Dad's Tales. California, Avenue Services. 2006. v.5, cuid23914 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Holy Titclamps. Ed. Laurence "Larry-bob" Roberts. n.15, 1995; cuid23915 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Hun Book of Bondage. Portland, The Hun. Issue 2, 2000; cuid23916 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hun Comics: 'B' series, 1987-1989; cuid23917 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. Jan 1988. n.1, cuid23918 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. June 1990. n.5, cuid23919 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. May 1992. n.6, cuid23920 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. Feb 1994. n.7, cuid23921 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Jan. 1996. n.8, cuid23922 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun. Aug 1996. n.9, cuid23923 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun, Dec 1997. n.10, cuid23924 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun. Nov 1998. n.11, cuid23925 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun. April 2002. n.12, cuid23926 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Jack & The Jungle (Tom of Finland). v.1/2/3, Undated; cuid23928 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - J.D.s., Undated; cuid23927 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Joezine. New York, Killer & Butch. n.2, Undated; cuid23929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Kake, by Tom of Finland. Barcelona, Candango. n.3, Undated; cuid23930 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kake. Barcelona, Candango. n.4, Undated; cuid23931 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kake. Barcelona, Candango. n.5, Undated; cuid23932 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kake, Special Edition: Greasy Rider. Denmark. n.21, Undated; cuid23933 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - The Male Figure. California, Bruce of Los Angeles. v.12, Undated; cuid23934 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Manorama. Washington D. C., Manorama Enterprises. November 1965. n.26, cuid23935 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Man Power! New York, Colt Studio. n.1, 1969; cuid23936 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Mar/April 1995. n.11, cuid23937 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Nov/Dec. 1996. n.21, cuid23938 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Mar/April 1997. n.23, cuid23939 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Sept/Oct. 1997. n.26, cuid23940 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Mentor. California, S.C.M.A. Fall, 1993; cuid23941 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mentor. California, S.C.M.A. n.7, Undated; cuid23942 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mentor. California, S.C.M.A. n.9, Undated; cuid23943 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Monstar: The Bruce LaBruce Story. Ed. Blab, Liza Lamonica, and k.d. kwellada. n.9, Undated; cuid23944 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. Spring, 1988; cuid23945 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade. Summer, 1989; cuid23946 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade. Winter, 1991; cuid23947 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade. Fall, 2004; cuid23948 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade, 2006; cuid23949 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Naked Magazine. Ed. Christopher Arroquun. California, Naked Magazine. v.1 n.2, Undated; cuid23950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Naked Magazine. Ed. Christopher Arroquun. California, Naked Magazine. v.1 n.4, Undated; cuid23951 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Nasty Boyz. Ed. Anthony Panther. New Jersey, ATKOL. 1995. v.1 n.1, cuid23952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Nasty Boyz. Ed. Anthony Panther. New Jersey, ATKOL. 1995. v.1 n.2, cuid23953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Nasty Boyz. Ed. Anthony Panther. New Jersey, ATKOL. 1995. v.1 n.3, cuid23954 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Not Fade Away: Selections from the NAMBLA Bulletin. New York, The North American Man/Boy Love Association, Undated; cuid23955 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Pansy Beat. Ed. Michael Economy, 1991; cuid23956 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Photographorama: A Photographic Comparison of Nationalities, Undated; cuid23957 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Pisszine. Ed. Massimo Magrini. n.6, Undated; cuid23958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. Winter 1994. n.2, cuid23959 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. Summer 1994. n.4, cuid23960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. 1994. Issue 5, cuid23961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. 1995. Issue 6, cuid23962 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. 1995. Issue 7, cuid23963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Pup. n.3, Undated; cuid23964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.1, 1992; cuid23965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.2, 1993; cuid23966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.3, Undated; cuid23967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.4, Undated; cuid23968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.5, 1994; cuid23969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.6, Undated; cuid23970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rim Reader. n.61, Undated; cuid23971 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sexvibe. Ed. Charlie Medrano. California, The Sex Essentials Network. Aug. 1994. n.3, cuid23972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Skirts. Ed. Pat McCunthy, Undated; cuid23973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sludgemaster. Texas. n.14, Undated; cuid23974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Sludgemaster. Texas. n.15, Undated; cuid23975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Southern Cumfort. Georgia, HOT! Publishing Company, 1994. v.1 n.3, cuid23976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Spunk: JizBiz Guide. v.3 n.6, Undated; cuid23977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Stall, by Tom of Finland, Stephen, Etienne. COQ International. n.2, Undated; cuid23978 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1978. n.42, cuid23979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1979. n.43, cuid23980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.44, Undated; cuid23981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.45, Undated; cuid23982 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1980. n.46, cuid23983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1980. n.47, cuid23984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.48, Undated; cuid23985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.49, Undated; cuid23986 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.50, Undated; cuid23987 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.51, Undated; cuid23988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.52, Undated; cuid23989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.57, Undated; cuid23990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.60, Undated; cuid23991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.61, Undated; cuid23992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.62, Undated; cuid23993 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. n.67, Undated; cuid23994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Tough Ride. v.1 n.3, Undated; cuid23995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - TRASH. Australia, D&W Enterprises, 1995. n.132, cuid23996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, n.74, Undated; cuid23997 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, n.76, Undated; cuid23998 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.126, cuid23999 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.127, cuid24000 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.128, cuid24001 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.129, cuid24002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1994. n.130, cuid24003 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1995. n.131, cuid24004 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1995. n.133, cuid24005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises. 1995. n.134, cuid24006 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1995. n.135, cuid24007 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1995. n.136, cuid24008 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.137, cuid24009 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.138, cuid24010 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.139, cuid24011 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.140, cuid24012 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1996. n.141, cuid24013 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.142, cuid24014 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.143, cuid24015 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.144, cuid24016 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1997. n.145, cuid24017 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.146, cuid24018 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.147, cuid24019 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.148, cuid24020 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.149, cuid24021 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.150, cuid24022 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.151, cuid24023 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1998. n.152, cuid24024 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 1999. n.153, cuid24025 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.154, cuid24026 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.155, cuid24027 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.156, cuid24028 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.157, cuid24029 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2000. n.158, cuid24030 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.159, cuid24031 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.160, cuid24032 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.161, cuid24033 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2001. n.162, cuid24034 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.163, cuid24035 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.164, cuid24036 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.165, cuid24037 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.166, cuid24038 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2002. n.167, cuid24039 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.168, cuid24040 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.169, cuid24041 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.170, cuid24042 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2003. n.171, cuid24043 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2004. n.172, cuid24044 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2004. n.173, cuid24045 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2004. n.175, cuid24046 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.176, cuid24047 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.177, cuid24048 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.178, cuid24049 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. n.179, cuid24050 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2005. nos. 180, 182, cuid24051 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.183, cuid24052 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.184, cuid24053 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.185, cuid24054 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.186, cuid24055 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2006. n.187, cuid24056 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2008. n.188, cuid24057 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2008. n.189, cuid24058 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2008. n.190, cuid24059 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.191, cuid24060 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.192, cuid24061 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.193, cuid24062 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - TRASH. D&W Enterprises, 2009. n.194, cuid24063 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Trim Studio Quarterly: "Spartacus". Trim Studio Quarterly, D.C. n.8, Undated; cuid24064 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Vagabond. Portfolio Minnesota, Vagabond Sales. 1964. n.1, cuid24065 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 1997. Issue 6, cuid24066 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Summer 1997. Issue 7, cuid24067 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 1999. Issue 11, cuid24068 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Water Boys.. Water Boys, Summer 1999. Issue 12, cuid24069 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 2000. Issue 13, cuid24070 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Autumn 2001. Issue 14, cuid24071 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Water Boys. Water Boys, Spring 2002. Issue 15, cuid24072 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - When Johnny Comes Marching Home Again. v.1 n.1, Undated; cuid24073 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Wrestling Tales 2. Mr. Xpress, 1991; cuid24074 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Zack Magazine. Ed. Rick Castro. v.1 n.1, Undated; cuid24075 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Series IV. Pornographic Film Tie-ins, 1977-1983, undated; 1 Linear Feet in one record carton.
  The tie-ins are arranged alphabetically by publication title.
  This series contains printed materials intended to accompany pornographic films (both film series and individual films); some films can also be found in this collection.
  - Below the Belt. Hardball. California Dream Machine Publishing, Undated; cuid24076 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Best of Al Parker, Undated; cuid24077 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Bigger the Better, Undated; cuid24078 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dangerous, Undated; cuid24079 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Falcon File: Don Talon. California, Falcon Studios. n.3, 1977; cuid24080 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Falcon File: Against the Rules. California, Falcon Studios. n.8, 1980; cuid24081 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Garage Sex. California, DPR Studios, Undated; cuid24082 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Jockstrap 2. California, Le Salon, 1982; cuid24083 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kept After School. The Nova Starline. n.2, Undated; cuid24084 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kinky Selection. Choc, Undated; cuid24085 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Loaded. Target Studios, Undated; cuid24086 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Loading Zone, Undated; cuid24087 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Love, Daddy. Close-up Productions. Feb. 1983. n.1, cuid24088 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Main Attraction. The Nova Starline, Undated; cuid24089 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Make My Buddy. A Nova Presentation, Undated; cuid24090 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ManMeat, Undated; cuid24091 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - A Matter of Size, From the Producers of Huge I & II, Undated; cuid24092 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Mike Arlen's Guys. London, Wetherby Studios. v.6, Undated; cuid24093 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - The Mountain Troopers, Sizzlin' Excerpts from Rangers, Undated; cuid24094 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Nuts and Bolts, Undated; cuid24095 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Ski Summit (Part 1) California, Falcon Studios, 1978; cuid24096 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Pit Stop. Surge Studios. Issue 1, Undated; cuid24097 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Probe One: Presenting Scenes from "4 in Hand", Undated; cuid24098 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Solo Suck Off, Undated; cuid24099 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - The Target Stable. New York, Target Studios, 1981; cuid24100 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Series V. Catalogs and Calendars, 1997-2006, undated; 1 linear foot in one record carton.
  This series contains erotic calendars; clothing and accessories catalogs; and catalogs and directories for gay pornographic films.
  The materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically by publication date.
  - Adam Gay Video Directory (7th edition), ed. Doug Lawrence. California, Knight Publishing, 1997; cuid24101 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Adam Gay Video Directory (9th edition), ed. Doug Lawrence. California, Knight Publishing, 1999; cuid24102 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Black Style. Berlin. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], 1996; cuid24103 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Butt Boy 2000: A Gay Pulp Fiction Calendar. California, SOHO Galleries, 1999; cuid24104 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Calendario Romano 2005 [Papal Calendar] ed. Piero Pazzi, cuid24105 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Colt Calendar 2003: Hairy Chested Men. California, Colt Studio, 2002; cuid24106 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Colt Calendar 2003: Leather Calendar. California, Colt Studio, 2002; cuid24107 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Falcon Film/Video Collection. California, Falcon Studios, Undated; cuid24108 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Fireboy. Montreal. 1997-1998 [Underwear catalogue], cuid24109 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Intermale Amsterdam Catalogue [Europe's international gay bookstore], Undated; cuid25272 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - cuir/latex n.2. France, IEM. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], 1998; cuid24110 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Male Nudes Diary. California, Athletic Model Guild. [Contains drawings by Tom of Finland], 1998; cuid24111 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Male Views, Catalog Number Seven, Undated; cuid25273 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Masta [leather video catalog], San Francisco, 1997; cuid25274 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Mr. S Leather and Fetters. California. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], Undated; cuid24112 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - The 1995 Annual Man Desk Calendar. California, State of Man Publishers, cuid24113 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - The Old Reliable Video Catalogue II. California, Old Reliable Tape Co., 1995; cuid24114 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Project X: International Hard Guide. Paris, PX Presse. [Bar/club guide], 1997; cuid24115 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Rexx. Paris, Rexx. [Leather clothing and accessories catalogue], Undated; cuid24116 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Rim Reader: Membership Listings, vol.3. California, T&T Productions. [Directory], 2001; cuid24117 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - RoB Catalog n.4. California/London/Amsterdam. [Clothing and accessories catalogue], Undated; cuid24118 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Titan Men Calendar 2006, California, TitanMen.com, cuid24119 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Series VI. Advertisements, 1998-2000, undated; 1 linear foot in one record carton.
  This series contains advertisements and mail-orders for pornographic publications and media; newsletters; leaflets; and pamphlets.
  The materials are arranged in alphabetical order by publisher, company, or sender.
  - 3rd World Video. New York, TWV Inc., 1998-2000; cuid24120 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Brown Hanky Journal. New Jersey, D&W Enterprises/Sludgemaster. Texas, 1998; cuid24121 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Colt Studios. California, 1998-2000; cuid24122 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Larry Townsend. California, 1998-2000; cuid24123 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous. [Incl. David Forest, MSP Video, Youth Development League], Undated; cuid24124 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Palm Drive Video. California, Undated; cuid24125 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Titan Media. California, 1999; cuid24126 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - TNT (T&T) Productions. California, Undated; cuid24127 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Tom of Finland Foundation. California, Undated; cuid24128 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Graphics, 1950-2007, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  This series is divided into two subseries:
  Subseries VII.A. Graphics and Illustrations, 1998-2000, undated
  Subseries VII.B. Japanese publications, 1950-2007, undated
  This series contains artist portfolios, illustrations, and visual ephemera, as well as Japanese Manga and related magazines.
  - Subseries VII.A. Graphics and Illustrations, 1998-2000, undated; 1.25 linear foot in 1 record carton and 1 flat file folder.
    This subseries is in alphabetical order by artist's last name.
    This collection contains artist portfolios, illustrations, miscellaneous visual ephemera, and accompanying documentation.
    - Bastille [photocopies], Undated; cuid24129 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Bill Ward [photocopies of drawings], Undated; cuid24130 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - CHAN/Fury161, "Pornotraffic" [magazine and promotional poster; correspondence; portfolio], 1997; cuid24131 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Domino [photocopies of drawings], 1980-1988; cuid24132 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - FUWA and other unidentified artists, drawings/illustrations depicting Japanese Manga characters in various bondage poses and related, 1996, 2000, undated; cuid25275 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Gengoroh Tagame [photocopies of drawings; G's-Men Tagame postcard collection; "biography notes" by Marshall], Undated; cuid24133 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - John Lindell, "After Tom of Finland"; "International" [Two illustrated booklet mock-ups; cover letter from Lindell], 1993; cuid24134 (Box 17, Folder 15)